Chad FALLOTIN

c.fallotin@gmail.com +61 415552679 * www.chadfallotin.com

I am a self-taught, recently graduated and highly motivated web developer, specialising in javascript stacks. I have a Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science, strong problem solving skills, as well as an ability to quickly get a hand on new technologies.

Education:

Mid-2017 - present: Udemy Online Courses*

FreeCodeCamp.com

Books*

2013-2016: Imperial College London - UK

Bachelor of Computer Sciences (2nd Class Honours)

2010-2013: Lycée Institut Stanislas - France

French Baccalauréat, Scientific section (1st Class Honours)

Work Experience:

January 2018 - present

TimberWolf, Brisbane. Australia

- Team Supervisor

- Planter

June 2017 - present

Brisbane, Australia

- Freelance Web developer

November 2016 - March 2017

The Computer Market, Brisbane, Australia

- IT Technician

Summer 2014-2016:

Isla Samba (Jewellery and Fashion accessories), Sainte-Maxime, France

- Salesman

- Security

Summer 2014:

Golf de Sainte-Maxime, France
- Assistant golf instructor

Key Skills:

Proficient in using the following web technologies:

- HTML, CSS (Scss), Javascript (ES6+, JQuery, D3)
- Vue / Angular 5
- NodeJS, Npm
- REST APIs
- MongoDB / Mongoose, MySQL
- Gulp, Webpack
- Responsive Design with Semantic UI, Bootstrap 4, Zurb

Agile development experience

Skills:

Languages:Tools:OS:JavaGitMacOS

Python Vscode / IntelliJ IDEA Linux (Ubuntu, Kali)

Windows

C / C++ Vi / Vim

Haskell Adobe Premier Pro Prolog Adobe AfterEffect

Projects / Awards:

Final Year Individual Project (2016)

ProSS: an Educational Tool for Learning Secret Sharing, Java (JavaFX)

https://github.com/joeharper1000/ProSS/

BlackRock Prize (2015)

Best Human Centered Design Group Project

Prototype mobile application serving as a daily assistant, designed to improve the daily life of people with Chronique Fatigue Syndrome (CFS) and their relatives.

Languages:

French Native

English Fluent (IELTS 7-8)
Spanish Intermediate (B1)

Interests:

Traveling | Golf (hcp 6) | Tennis (30) | Bodybuilding | Surf | Piano | SpeedCubing | Books | Day-trading | Rocket League | Video Filming/Editing